{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "JSON stands for...",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "JavaScript Object Notation",
            "option2": "Java Object Notation",
            "option3": "JavaScript Object Normalization",
            "option4": "JavaScript Object-Oriented Notation",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "JSON is a _____ for storing and transporting data.",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "xml format",
            "option2": "text format",
            "option3": "",
            "option4": "",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the creator of JSON?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "Alvin Alexander",
            "option2": "Rasmus Lerdorf",
            "option3": "Douglas Crockford",
            "option4": "Jesse James Garrett",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The principles of software engineering are applied during software engineering process by ____ .",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "All of the mentioned below",
            "option2": "Mechanical engineers",
            "option3": "Electrical engineers",
            "option4": "Software engineers",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "A second-year college student is usually called a what?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "sophomore",
            "option2": "senior",
            "option3": "freshman ",
            "option4": "junior ",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which HTML tag is used to create a hyperlink?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "<link>",
            "option2": "<href>",
            "option3": "<a>",
            "option4": "<hyperlink>",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is a popular front-end framework for building user interfaces in JavaScript?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "Django",
            "option2": "Angular",
            "option3": "Flask",
            "option4": "Node.js",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is not associated with web socket communication?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "http",
            "option2": "wss",
            "option3": "https",
            "option4": "ws",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following property is used to control the space between the border and content in a table?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "border",
            "option2": "padding",
            "option3": "margin",
            "option4": "",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "ich of the following is the Web application equivalent to querySelectorAll()?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "#()",
            "option2": "&()",
            "option3": "!()",
            "option4": "$()",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "React.js is written in which language?",
            "type":"input",
            "answer": "javascript"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following directives is used to start an angularJS application?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "ng-app",
            "option2": "ng-init",
            "option3": "ng-repeat",
            "option4": "ng-model",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the JavaScript keyword used to define a function?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "var",
            "option2": "function",
            "option3": "let",
            "option4": "const",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which CSS property is used to specify the width of an element?",
            "type":"input",
            "answer": "width"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Vue JS?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "Scripting Language",
            "option2": "A framework",
            "option3": "Programming Language",
            "option4": "Directives",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which font format is used in web pages?",
            "type":"input",
            "answer": "WOFF"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many classes does bootstrap grid system has?",
            "type":"input",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following CSS Property controls how an element is positioned?",
            "type":"mcq",
            "option1": "fix",
            "option2": "set",
            "option3": "static",
            "option4": "position",
            "answer": "2"
        }
    ]
}